Hi, my name's Amy Kistler, and I'm going to talk to you a little bit about the different types of personal trainers.
There's all different types of personal trainers.
You have personal trainers that specialize in yoga.
You've got personal trainers that specialize in karate.
You have personal trainers that specialize in dance, that specialize in core, that specialize in fitness.
There is a huge range of different types of personal trainers.
If you're considering getting a personal trainer, you want to make sure that you're aware of what you want your goals to be so that you can get a personal trainer that's right for you.
For example, if a personal trainer specializes in core exercises, they're going to be doing exercises that are related to the core area.
Just because we say core doesn't mean it's all ab exercises.
It means the whole body.
Personal trainers don't always specialize in one activity.
Some have a wide range of experience, and they're open to all different types of training.
For example, some trainers do core training.
They also do full body weight training.
Some break up training to do biceps and tris, and then some break it up and do back and bis.
All different types of trainers do different types of exercises.
They train sports players.
They train the average Joe.
They train somebody that just wants to plain and simply lose weight.
They train someone that wants to put on a little bit more muscle mass.
And they also train people that are going to get married.
So they do basic overall training, which is what most people out there are looking for.
There are personal trainers that are specialized in specific sports.
So, for example, we have personal trainers that can help you improve your basketball skills, that can help you improve your volleyball skills, that can help improve you in running.
You can also get a personal trainer to help write you a program on how to progress and how to work up to running in a marathon.